<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><docs>https://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><title>Posts on Philipp Nagel</title><link>https://blog.philippnagel.com/post/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Philipp Nagel</description><image><title>Posts on Philipp Nagel</title><link>https://blog.philippnagel.com/post/</link><url>https://source.unsplash.com/collection/983219/2000x1322</url></image><ttl>1440</ttl><generator>After Dark 9.2.3 (Hugo 0.85.0)</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 20:59:24 UT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.philippnagel.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why are there almost no Magic Apps on Android?</title><link>https://blog.philippnagel.com/post/magic-apps/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 20:52:59 UT</pubDate><guid>https://blog.philippnagel.com/post/magic-apps/</guid><description>During the Covid-19 pandemic I developed an interest in magic. The show kind of magic.
Naturally I became especially interested in combining magic and programming.
What I noticed was that most magic apps are only available on iOS. I asked Marc Kerstein, a well known app magician and programmer, about that.
TL,DR:
He only has personal capacity to develop on iOS Android has a piracy problem Due to the small amount of potential users the apps are expensive.</description><category domain="https://blog.philippnagel.com/categories/apps">Apps</category><category domain="https://blog.philippnagel.com/categories/magic">Magic</category><content:encoded>During the Covid-19 pandemic I developed an interest in magic. The show kind of magic.
Naturally I became especially interested in combining magic and programming.
What I noticed was that most magic apps are only available on iOS. I asked Marc Kerstein, a well known app magician and programmer, about that.
TL,DR:
He only has personal capacity to develop on iOS Android has a piracy problem Due to the small amount of potential users the apps are expensive. iOS users are known to spend more on apps than their Android counterparts He pointed me towards this post of his on Reddit: https://www.reddit.com/r/Magic/comments/fqj99c/new_app_amalgam_by_marc_kerstein/.
Some interesting links:
https://www.vision-tricks.com/ https://marckerstein.com/ https://apps.apple.com/ch/app/cyber-magic/id1498541157 https://unlistedtrick.com/ https://www.augmented-magic.com/ https://www.magicapps.co/ https://tkjiang.com/ https://nicolai-friedrich.de/home/ https://jordinexus.com/digital-magic/</content:encoded></item><item><title>Crypto Crystal Ball 2021 Review</title><link>https://blog.philippnagel.com/post/crypto-crystal-ball-2021-review/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 14:15:58 UT</pubDate><guid>https://blog.philippnagel.com/post/crypto-crystal-ball-2021-review/</guid><description>1729.com asked to review the 2021 predictions for the crypto space compiled by Soona Amhaz.
The collected predictions are mostly interesting and made by even more interesting people. However I believe that most of them have little more than entertainment value due to the lack of accurately defined target conditions.
For example it is unclear how one would assess the following statements as fulfilled:
&amp;ldquo;Bitcoin continues to cross the chasm, deepening its institutional adoption along the “digital gold” narrative.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[1729.com asked to review the 2021 predictions for the crypto space compiled by Soona Amhaz.
The collected predictions are mostly interesting and made by even more interesting people. However I believe that most of them have little more than entertainment value due to the lack of accurately defined target conditions.
For example it is unclear how one would assess the following statements as fulfilled:
 &amp;ldquo;Bitcoin continues to cross the chasm, deepening its institutional adoption along the “digital gold” narrative.&amp;rdquo; - Alok Vasudev
 or
 &amp;ldquo;The crypto industry will have a record year of consolidation as the M&amp;amp;A market heats up and fintech / banks scoop up crypto companies.&amp;rdquo; - Kinjal Shah
 and
 &amp;ldquo;2021 will be the year of decentralizing the stack. The critical protocols for decentralized APIs, oracles and storage are near production ready to support current Ethereum usage. Soon it will seem foolish and unsafe to run a dApp on centralized infrastructure.&amp;rdquo; - Eva Beylin
 There are several good examples to take note from:
 &amp;ldquo;We’ll see $100k BTC, $2k ETH, and a Coinbase IPO. Black swan perhaps one of the Grayscale products trades at a discount in 2nd half of 2021, but that’s a much smaller chance than the first three.&amp;rdquo; - Joey Krug
 or
 &amp;ldquo;EIP 1559 will be live by end of 2021. Total DEX trading volume in 2021 will break $1T.&amp;rdquo; - Clinton Bembry Jr.
 and
 &amp;ldquo;The bitcoin price: will go down will go up Buckle up!&amp;rdquo; - Amiti Uttarwar
 Tweet me @philippnag. I will be thinking about my predictions for 2022. Happy to hear about your recommended, decentralized betting products to get some skin in the game.
]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>